Lechmere vs. NLRB Company Legal Files 6008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lechmere vs. NLRB Company Legal Files
1987-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Labor Relations Board (NLRB)
Lechmere
6008
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
5757753
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 08, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 13, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
United States.; United States. National Labor Relations Board
5757753
- BNA Plus 1992, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Union Bulletins and Briefings, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Newington Summer 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Newington - Summer and Fall 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Newington 6/87, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Newington Incident Log T.B. Copy, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Copies of Ads, Handouts, Literature, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Misc. Newington, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Supreme Court Info, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Supreme Court Info, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)